She must hold many men in her arms to find the one man she could love!
BUtterfield 8 is a drama film directed by Daniel Mann.
Gloria Wandrous, a promiscuous fashion model, falls in love with Weston Liggett, the
hard drinking son of a working class family who has married into money.
Gloria Wandrous, played by Elizabeth Taylor.
Weston Liggett, played by Laurence Harvey.
Steve Carpenter, played by Eddie Fisher.
Emily Liggett, played by Dina Merrill.
Mrs. Wandrous, played by Mildred Dunnock.
Mrs. Fanny Thurber, played by Betty Field.
BUtterfield 8 is a 1960 American drama film directed by Daniel
Mann, starring Elizabeth Taylor and Laurence Harvey.
Taylor won her first Academy Award for her performance in a leading role.
The film was based on a 1935 novel of the same name by John O'Hara.
The film explores themes of pianist, modeling, marrying money, 1930s, mink coat.
The tone is emotional.